PRIVACY POLICY

1. PRELIMINARY STATEMENT

1.1. This Privacy Policy explains how ANY.RUN FZCO (hereinafter

‘ANY.RUN’) collects, processes, and shares personal data of users of

our website and services. ANY.RUN takes privacy seriously and adheres

to principles of transparency, data minimization, purpose limitation,

accuracy, storage limitation, integrity, confidentiality and accountability.

1.2. Acceptance of Terms of Use shall mean automatically full and

unconditional acceptance of this Privacy Policy by the User. ANY.RUN

reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy and is not obliged to

notify the User. The changes will come into force upon their publication

on the Website except otherwise is provided by the updated version of

this Privacy Policy. User’s continued usage of the Services shall signify

User’s acceptance of such changes.

1.3. While using the ANY.RUN Services User has to ensure that the files/ the

URL User are about to submit contain no personal data of any third party

or if so, User have the full and informed consent of those third parties or

the statutory right to transfer these personal data. ANY.RUN is not

responsible for any conflict arising according to the submitting of

personal data of third parties involved in your files/ URL.

1.4. Please be aware that interactive analysis as a part of Services provided

by ANY.RUN is not confidential unless otherwise stated. User can turn

on privacy mode in the advanced menu before start using Services.

1.5. The Privacy policy is effective from July 24, 2024.

2. COLLECTING AND PROCESSING OF USER’S PERSONAL DATA

2.1. Purposes for Collection \& Usage of User Personal Information.

ANY.RUN may use User Personal Information for the following

purposes:

• Providing our Services

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

• Improving our Services

• Communicating with Users

• Verifying User’s identity

• Registering users for promotions and events

• Responding to technical support questions and concerns

• Contacting users for marketing, advertising, and sales purposes

• Responding to questions and feedback

• Conducting market research and analysis

• Conducting internal research for technological development

• Continuously evaluating and improving the online user experience

• Network and information security

• Fraud prevention

• To permit access to our facilities

• Reporting suspected criminal acts

• Compliance with the law or to protect the rights, property, or safety

of ANY.RUN, our users, or others

• Sending educational (training) materials to User, links to

educational materials and invitations to webinars and educational

demo presentations (including but not limited to ‘Sandbox training’)

Please see below the most common cases of using your data by

ANY.RUN:

Registration Data: When registering an account, ANY.RUN collects

your name and business email address to identify your account and

send transactional emails.

Legal basis: Performance of a contract.

Contact Form Data: If User contacts us via the form, ANY.RUN collects

your phone number, email and Company name to respond.

Legal basis: Legitimate interests to respond to inquiries.

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

Payment Data: To process payments, our processor FastSpring collects

your name, card details, payment date and ID. Legal basis: Performance

of a contract.

ANY.RUN also processes Personal Information as necessary for its

legitimate interests as follows:

• Marketing and advertising: Unless User opts out as described below,

ANY.RUN uses User Personal Information regarding products and

services User has ordered, or which potentially may interest User, as

necessary to provide User information about the products and

services that might interest User in accordance with applicable law.

• Network and information security, fraud prevention, and reporting

suspected criminal acts: In the event of fraud, a security incident, or a

suspected criminal act, ANY.RUN would examine Personal

Information that appeared to be linked to the incident as necessary to

determine what happened, remediate, report to the authorities, and

prevent a recurrence.

2.2. Web servers store details of user’s operating system and browser used,

a webpage from which user comes to the Website, pages that user visits

on the Website, and IP address assigned to a user by user’s Internet

service provider (ISP). With the exception of user’s IP address, in

following cases the personal data is collected and stored only if a user

chooses to submit it to ANY.RUN:

2.2.1. When registering, for identification of your account and

transactional email ANY.RUN collect:

• Email address

2.2.2. When User uses contact form in order to correspond with us, to

reach Userback ANY.RUN collect:

• Name

• Email address

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

2.2.3. When paying, to provide User with the paid services (creation,

prolongation and payment subscriptions) ANY.RUN uses

PADDLE payment processing.

These third party service providers have their own privacy policies

addressing how they use such information. User can read PADDLE

privacy policy on their website.

According to information provided by PADDLE PCI DDS was developed

to protect consumers of PADDLE and their data no matter where they

shop or what channel they use. PADDLE renews PCI Level 1

compliance every year, the highest level of certification possible.

2.2.4. To protect service from attacks and for a recognizing different

user types, on every http request ANY.RUN collects:

• IP/Country/Provider

• URL/Query/Browser/Referrer/Cookie/Headers

2.3. ANY.RUN uses User data to:

2.3.1. Provide individual service, support and advertisement for a user.

2.3.2. Inform user about ANY.RUN new products and services.

2.3.3. In the event that ANY.RUN are involved in a merger, acquisition or

asset sale, ANY.RUN may disclose your personal data to the

prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

2.4. User hereby agrees that ANY.RUN could use your email address User

have entered to send out a newsletter from which User can unsubscribe

at any time by clicking on the deactivation link provided in every

newsletter or in your own profile by clicking on the checkmark to disable.

3. SHARING USER’S PERSONAL DATA

ANY.RUN shares data with service providers under contract to process data

on our behalf for the above purposes.

3.1. User’s personal data will remain only with ANY.RUN, its affiliates, and its

service providers and will not be available to third parties except

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

situations when ANY.RUN is obligated to disclose such information by

the law.

3.2. Personal data shared with service providers will be used only to perform

ANY.RUN services. Providing your personal data to ANY.RUN User

agrees that ANY.RUN could submit relevant information to the following

services in compliance with General Data Protection Regulation

(GDPR):

• Email services: MailerLite and Amazon SES to send and receive

emails. MailerLite may also display pop-ups and email collection

forms on our site.

• Payment service providers: PADDLE or its affiliates in order to receipt

payments.

3.3. ANY.RUN may use third-party services such as Google Analytics that

collect, monitor and analyze user’s information in order to increase

ANY.RUN Service’s functionality. These third-party service providers

have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such

information. User can read privacy policy of third-party service providers

on their websites.

4. DATA RETENTION

4.1. ANY.RUN stores personal data as long as it is required to perform the

Services to the user providing no legal contradictions exist (in a case of

retention periods required by trade or tax regulations etc.).

4.2. At any time User may exercise your right to have your personal data

removed, provided that no legal requirement opposes deletion or the

data is necessary for the fulfilment of a contractual obligation of

ANY.RUN.

4.3. Retention Period

4.3.1. Registration data (Section 2.2.1) is stored the whole time user is

using the service.

4.3.2. Contact us form data (Section 2.2.2) is stored as support ticket for

an indefinite amount of time or deleted upon a request from the

user.

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

4.3.3. Payment information (Section 2.2.3) is stored as long as the

service is provided to the user, and can be deleted only provided

that no legal requirements exist, for example, in the case of

storage periods required as a result of trade or tax.

4.3.4. HTTP request data (Section 2.4.4) is stored for 30 days.

5. RIGHT TO OBTAIN AND CORRECT INFORMATION

5.1. User has the right:

• of access to Personal Data relating to User;

• to correct any mistakes in User Personal Data;

• to ask us to stop contacting User with direct marketing;

• to restrict or prevent your Personal Data being processed;

• to erasure.

5.2. In order to request any of actions required please send a message to

ANY.RUN contact email indicated in Terms of Use.

5.3. The deletion of user’s personal data will be completed immediately

unless ANY.RUN is legally obliged to store such information.

6. CHILDREN'S PRIVACY

6.1. ANY.RUN does not knowingly collect information from anyone under the

age of 16. ANY.RUN is directed for persons older than 16 years old.

Persons under 16 are not allowed to register and use ANY.RUN without

parent permission.

7. COOKIES

7.1. ANY.RUN established its own Cookie policy and applies cookie banner

to comply with relevant privacy legislation.

8. SECURITY

8.1. ANY.RUN applies organizational and technical security measures to

protect the data supplied by visitors and users against manipulation,

loss, destruction and unsanctioned access by third parties.

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

9. UNSUBSCRIBING FROM EMAILS:

In addition, User may cancel or modify the email communications User

had chosen to receive from ANY.RUN by following the instructions

contained in emails from us. Alternatively, User may email ANY.RUN at

unsubscribe@any.run with your request, stating 'Unsubscribe' in the

header and what email addresses User wishes not to receive HARMAN

emails. Within a reasonable period, ANY.RUN shall ensure that such

email addresses are unsubscribed.

10. Cross-Border Data Transfers: In order to provide our Services, your

Personal Information may need to be accessed by our entities across

the world. Before transferring your Personal Information to any of our

entities across the world, ANY.RUN will ensure all required transfer

mechanisms are in place to ensure an adequate level of protection for

the transfer of your Personal Information.

11. Each user is fully responsible for the legality of uploaded Content

including Personal Data of User or Personal Data of any third parties.

Using the Content through the Services shall not infringe any personal

data rights of any third parties. User shall not input, upload, or otherwise

provide any information to Public submissions that violates or infringes

any third party rights, including but not limited to personal data that

would violate the rights of any data subject under the EU General Data

Protection Regulation (GDPR), the applicable data protection laws of the

United Arab Emirates, or any other relevant jurisdiction. User shall be

solely responsible for ensuring that all information inputed into the

Software is properly authorized for use as contemplated herein and does

not violate any laws or rights of any third party. ANY.RUN assumes no

responsibility for any infringing information supplied by User. If any third

party alleges that information provided by User violates their rights, User

shall fully cooperate with ANY.RUN in investigating and defending such

claim. In the event any information supplied by User results in an

infringement claim, User shall indemnify and hold harmless ANY.RUN

pursuant to the indemnification provision of this clause.

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/

DISCLAIMER: Any personal data uploaded by User to Public

submissions can not be identified by ANY.RUN as personal data

therefore any request made by User or any third party in relation to such

personal data can not be satisfied by ANY.RUN. When uploading

personal data to Public Submissions User clearly understands that such

data is being seen by unlimited number of Users. User guarantees that

consent from third parties on uploading their Personal data was

obtained by User. Any third party claims related to personal data

disclosure shall be a sole responsibility of User that uploaded data in

Public Submissions.

ANYRUN FZCO – Dubai Silicon Oasis, Techno Hub 1,

Unit 21, 60th Street, Dubai, UAE

support@any.run

https://any.run/
